saisd.net 2018-06-30

# SAISD Privacy Policy

Registration is now online for current and new students for the 2018-19 school year!   [Register today](https://saisdenroll.schoolmint.net/)   
¡Inscripciones están disponibles en línea para el año escolar 2018-19!   [Inscríbase hoy](https://saisdenroll.schoolmint.net/)

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. **What do we use your information for?** Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)  
 
  * To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.   
 
  * To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information.  **Note: If at anytime you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.  
 **
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

**Do we use cookies?**

We do not use cookies.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This Privacy Policy applies only to the SAISD website that you currently are visiting. It does not apply to data collected through our student information systems, such as iData Portal and ITTCS, which are protected by the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act, or FERPA.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

**C hanges to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contact Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by using the information below:

Online Privacy Policy  
c/o San Antonio Independent School District  
141 Lavaca, San Antonio TX 78210  
Tel: 210.554.2200
